# **BERKE PERIM**

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER

# PERSONAL DETAILS

#### ADDRESS

Eskişehir Türkive

#### PHONE

905389841095

#### EMAIL

berkeperim@gmail.com

#### DATE OF BIRTH

08/10/1995

#### LINKS

LinkedIn

berkeperim.github.io

### SKILLS

JavaScript

• • • • •

jQuery

• • • •

React

. . . . 0

NodeJS

• • • • •

PHP

• • • •

Laravel

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$   $\circ$ 

HTML5

• • • • •

CSS3

• • • •

MvSOL

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$ 

SQI

• • • • 0

Git

. . . . .

Adobe Photoshop

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$ 

Figma

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$   $\circ$ 

## LANGUAGES

English

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$ 

#### PROFILE

My name is Berke and I enjoy creating things that live on the internet. I'm a Turkey based Frontend Developer and a bit of Backend Developer:)

I have hands on experience using front-end technologies and frameworks like **Javascript**, **ReactJS**, **jQuery** and back-end technologies and frameworks like **PHP**, **NodeJS**, **Laravel**. I am currently working on **ReactJS** and **NodeJS** to further my proficiency in these languages.

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## Frontend Developer, PersonaClick

Istanbul

Sep 2023 — Present

- Run the frontend development processes of huge e-commerce brands using the algorithms and personalized data of the product developed by the company.
- $\cdot\;$  Using Javascript (ES6) while running this frontend development process
- · Clients included Watsons, Vivense, Atelier Rebul and more

## Full Stack Developer, Esdisis Bilişim

Eskişehir

Aug 2019 — Jul 2022

- Worked on Frontend, Backend and Database optimizing parts of the existing web-based real-time call system that includes features like Product & Stock & Logistic Management, Customer Management, Calendar, To-Do etc.
- Led the frontend developments in the company's new CRM project and took an active role in the planning, design and determination of the technologies to be used from the beginning of the project until I left
- Used PHP, Codeigniter, Javascript, jQuery, Tailwind technologies while developing frontend and backend in these projects. Also used MySQL for database optimization.

## Front end Developer, Bulutsoft Bilişim

Eskişehir

Mar 2019 — Jun 2019

- I was part of the team that developed a CRM application for travel agencies using NodeJS and Javascript
- In addition to this, I was also part of a team that developed booking websites for clients. I worked as a Full Stack Developer in these projects
- · I used Laravel and VueJS libraries in these projects
- While developing these booking websites, I worked with the JSON data that comes with the API of the developed CRM application

## Front end Developer, Alpha Creative

Eskişehir

Jul 2018 — Jan 2019

- Developed and maintained code for in-house and client websites primarily using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery
- Manually tested sites in various browsers and mobile devices to ensure cross-browser compatibility and responsiveness
- · Websites were developed dynamically using PHP and MySQL and deployed

## Front end Developer, Pill Digital

Eskişehir

Jun 2017 — Sep 2017

 Developed and maintained code for in-house and client websites primarily using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery

- Manually tested sites in various browsers and mobile devices to ensure cross-browser compatibility and responsiveness
- · Websites were developed dynamically using PHP and MySQL and deployed

# EDUCATION

# **Bachelor, Anadolu University**

Eskişehir

Sep 2013 — Jan 2019

I studied in the Department of Computer Education and Instructional Technology.I received pedagogical formation training. I graduated with honors.